(Sheldon:)I read they were illegally squatting
on Indian land.
(Sheldon:)Personally, I think what we did
to the Native Americans was wrong,
(Sheldon:)but this is your favourite show,
not mine.
(Sheldon:)Oh, look at little Laura Ingalls,
eating that peanut butter sandwich.
(Sheldon:)Peanut butter?
(Raj:)Huh...
(Sheldon:)That's strange,
(Sheldon:)since peanut butter wasn't introduced
until the early 1900s.
(Sheldon:)If I knew this show was
about time travel,
(Sheldon:)I would have watched it much sooner.
(TURNS OFF TV)
(Amy:)You're trying to get back at me
(Amy:)for what I said
about Raiders of the Lust Ark.
(Sheldon:)That's silly.
(Sheldon:)Almost as silly as Dr. Baker
having a telephone,
(Sheldon:)since telephones only existed
in large cities at that time.
(Sheldon:)This is more like Little House
on the Preposterous.
(Amy:)Sheldon, we're in a relationship.
(Amy:)When you get angry, just tell me.
(Amy:)You don't need to seek revenge.